I've got a lot of the radio meeting with the State Council for Monday, May 17.
I'm a student who provides you a recognition of outstanding heat service to exactly
the State Security, the State Security, the State Security, different white and dark outs and
same thing, please.
Well, the kind of government will say this group of individuals here have brought
national and worldwide attention to the world community, because they have beauty marks, and they care about our beauty.
I don't know what I'm doing because we're doing beauty.
And they started beauty balls, the restaurants, the same beauty thing, more of those, well.
The same guy says, sorry, we go back, I don't know.
The dog has to agree.
And I don't know if that go back.
I don't know if they're always, no, or we're having anything to just walk.
So, back in the National War, the National War, the National War, both of the side area,
but the curtain, they really set up.
They really set up, they really set up, they just hand in, and it started community,
didn't ask questions.
There wasn't judgment.
Do they know that they're all got things back in the other time?
Yes, they did.
They really did what they were supposed to do.
The attention we got, the community, is the attention that you can't hide.
Some of the attention from all around the world.
I don't think it's any story, it's a fact of magic.
That's the story.
Is that what you got?
Oh, all of you got cards.
So, the 30 best story.
On the left side of the story, we got a community vote.
Yeah.
We call this vote.
We call it a number.
No, no, I'm sure.
We saw it on the PC.
It was a one with a bloodster vote, a one that we were on.
And one of the main 30 women are all women.
We've had the House 1 and 1.
You know, the city.
A couple of them journey.
Yeah.
Or so get the cards and everything.
Yeah, I know that none of you get the assault recognition.
Yeah, absolutely.
But what you get is there to be right now.
So, as a capital, we want to recognize you.
Thank you.
That's some trouble.
I'm sorry.
We guys.
You're really kidding?
Me.
You're going to be good.
We're going to be good.
It's been a couple of years.
We're going to be.
Probably did.
It was the first couple of parents.
I'm going to try.
Before we send the gender, the Saturday committee.
If you could prove that I was behind.
Good morning.
A second.
He's here.
Hot.
Purple.
Who's there?
I'm here.
The Secretary of State Annual Contractor role of the C-20-16A,
who is concrete, the convrupal mayor.
Which we agree with.
Second.
Part of the debate.
The debate.
The vote.
Senator.
The abstinence.
The vote.
This is something that we're working on for a bad.
It's a year and a half.
Pride comes to us today and a big single point at the belly of the city council.
It's a big single point at the belly of the city council.
It's a big day.
Yeah.
Something we're happy we're happy to be able to have you to amazing if I rock a power line.
It comes up for the work from the need of this year.
need to hear, which is how to get our internet.
If that item is severed, the sitting, this is exciting.
And let's have a little bit of a little bit of a
thing to be able to have a phone or internet service
and stuff like that as compared to that.
What this does is gives us a redundant segment.
The internet connection, it's not as large as our current home,
but it's enough to handle any critical data that we need,
so this is our home.
And you know what people want to get on to any of the offerings
and sitting hands that are over a lot of here,
within the total.
All right, you said a big single point of failure,
and it's kind of a safety issue as well,
since we host our police.
of this building, our dispatches are on a nine-and-one system that is not part of the
army, near net service, it's time to this building, but they do utilize it further than
the start of the building. So any 90 of these homes that come in would be affected if we
have to clear that out to our area and continue. And as you can see, I've looked through those things.
We don't have a huge number of options. Currently we do have both as a binary provider. The
other small options we have are through AT&T and Sparkline for a binary connection. As you can see,
I'm going to close the Sparkline's A-min with the map for me and I'm going to order it from
a month, but I'm going to say thank you. That's a day of pay, which means we won't be shared
in that way when we're like anyone. So if you have any questions, I did look at the savings between
the fuel, is about more than half of the earlier year. I do have plans to utilize this connection, so
just me, or thank for something around you. I think it would be useful to use this area in action and
think in terms of what it's currently, where I need to pay for something that's not going to be
alive. I'm going to present this on track. I'm not going to be one of the tools you need. I cannot tell you
that. I assume that it has, or it should be gone here.
So, you said that this is going to be useful, so you can jump to the point that we have to pay attention to.
How does that affect you in your position?
Yeah.
Excuse me.
That's what it's saying.
I mean, what the worst case scenario is about.
How does that affect you on a day-to-day because you're simple paying for this?
It's not going to be something worth paying for or not using.
It's just to clarify, it will be a conjunction with our own interaction.
The AT&T, the AT&T, the AT&T, the fiber link that we have just for our 911 dispatch, which is part of the 911 system.
What this will do is conjunction with a current system is ideally used to execute some of our data.
The G's are always the right need on system, but it's things we can split that off on to.
It's a very important thing to remember, so it has a constant dedicated impact on the AT&T and the AT&T.
And with the opinions, right now, it's just shared the same bandwidth with all of the rest of the incoming AT&T data that the city has.
That's everything for our interaction.
Connections that we have could be as well as the spire and if our connections from our outside buildings that come in,
I'll share that same pipeline in the data.
This is as a little bit more emphasis, basically prioritize the data.
The one thing about what's over our existing systems is there.
One of the highest, one of the systems is on the network that the client has a very constant state of connection.
Because if that's interrupted, and any of that's where you start having problems for the phone to start crossing,
that's where being a local problem is losing action.
This helps to eliminate at least a few things in that machine on to the day-to-day side of the thing.
The phone on the side is if something were happening in that connection, it's similar to everything that we're working with.
That means that if there are a certain data happening on this, like if we go over most of the things that's commercial,
in the connection it's not connected, certainly a certain space needs to be charged for overages.
There is no connection.
That means.
I want the situation of this and why I don't suck people, I can take it off of this time, so.
I'll suck you.
Can we work?
I don't think so.
That's right.
We're 12.
We're going to move on.
We're going to have better support from you, sitting in my home.
We're going to have to come up with some emergency solutions for you.
We need to drive this over.
Let's go.
We are supposed to get approval to a blackbird and be a secret.
I wanted to see solutions for all of you to support for our shelter.
And if you're fired at the work of production of the city, this isn't.
This is supposed to happen.
We are supposed to hold for all funds, but we need to direct that to the most force of the human form.
I have to show you.
I have to.
Thank you.
But things like our service to him, ground day and session, evening, and agonies on this,
on day, fully at at beef point one.
So, please.
Just in the game.
Let's go.
I think.
It's good.
To.
And.
They come about to the.
They come about to.
This is part of that.
They have.
On the.
They ask for us to do something to select representatives, I personally feel like if I shouldn't restrict any of you from going, I want to go, I want to go, I want to land.
If you want to land, you should go with land. The only thing to change is that we have to make no need to be careful.
I don't know what to do, I don't know what to do, I don't know what to do.
If you want to ask questions, do you have questions?
Do you have any questions that you have to do?
Do you have any questions that you can ask?
Do you have any questions that you haven't done?
I think we were at that time, we did.
I didn't think it would be weird.
The last time we spoke, that we would have a version of this night,
and he actually talked about something here.
If you could be interested in questions,
and there's something to come up with.
But Christian Jackson, you know,
we're aware that we'll be able to get into there
before we back to the post.
That's something we should have to look at.
So do you want to explain that to me?
Can you explain something to me?
I've got a change to what we need to do.
So the point where I'm going to explain.
Do you want to be able to know this?
And it's a special question.
But he's got a complicated idea.
It's a way of life to talk.
But it's an easy conversation.
That we need to learn that.
That to the right.
To the right.
That's like when you make a question that we can all get.
Do you want to be able to go?
You know how we can.
So we're going to go around there.
Just with this side.
You did want to go.
So I've said to come back to you.
You've done it.
Well, I'll be there.
We can.
Because the.
The.
the household to approve a piece of ordinance. We don't have what it is. They are not
telling us what it is. But because of the time frame that they have outlined to us, we
want to kind of give you a hint that one of the oldest of Daniel in the year that could have
come back and do four or four weeks and we need you.
And there are very strict timeframes on things that happen.
This is the type of process that's set out by a different constitution,
and by different sections.
We do not have a much complicated,
and actually not a lot of instances about it.
But I didn't want anybody to be surprised,
although we all are going to be surprised as to what we're not in.
I don't know if you could be surprised by the nature of the proceedings,
that the most of the work that is held in an administrative edition
is whether you sit at work,
but perhaps in itself it's all in the process
and there are things that you have to do.
It doesn't matter what your thoughts on the question.
Whatever the question is,
or you're required by a lot of things sort of snacks,
and there are certain timeframes that can happen.
So that's to do it in the same way,
or the timeframes that I had to do sort of things.
So with that background,
I mean, I could go into,
it's a nice detail that she wants,
which I hope it's not a little walk.
Because really, I just want to make sure you understand
the general parameters of how this thing works.
They filed a petition with the City Board.
She asked it officially, logged in,
and within three days of that happening,
I, as the City Attorney, can't do certified,
but highly that they can't do this question,
that they actually burdened with the question.
I do not think it is to be old within that three days of time
you could be able to,
I can actually grab and sniff that to the City Clerk,
and then things proceed from there.
Of course, the biggest degree with the wording that I think is required
and that the ability to support them,
that it just gets a lot more complicated.
But generally, there's two avenues that this thing can get.
Once it's then officially served by,
then you can counsel, have to address the question,
and you can may or have to,
call it as a question for the council.
If you can prove it, then as it is written,
or for, as I may have modified it, then it's essentially,
if you don't approve it, then that's,
that's what triggers and then start getting,
starting to get signatures,
and if they get enough signatures within you.
of the time frame that goes to a vote of the people and the citizens of Lyon are made
in a decision as to whether or not this becomes a view ordinance would sit. That's very
generally the prangers account of works. A couple of things that I can give you information
on that we do know. First of all, there are comments that this one can be an ordinance change.
It's not a charter change, they're asking for it. That's very significant. Sign up all
if it goes to a lunch. There are target dates for the actual election. You can act with the election
of the election board. We try to figure out all the time for names of everything. The party dates for the election
would be September 4th or October 12th. If that's there to an election, the cost of the election
would work by the city and it would be in the neighborhood of about $5,000. We don't have much
of it. The law of the suppliers that we paid with that election. There are this definition
of those that say, this is five-time. I apologize for that. We compared half of the numbers.
They're going to be involved with this process and it's possible that some things may happen when
the election is not able to require a city clerk to act and so we need that action for this.
The numbers and juniors that are required for the decision to be sufficient is one for the people
to vote in the last general election of the city and that people may be able to vote for action
that can June 2020. There are two thousand four hundred and twelve votes passed.
It requires one quarter of that number. So the addition to the requirements is in the green signatures.
Now let's say the juniors are more to be sufficient and the only other thing that I can
Thank you. Thank you for the subject matter of this. The addition is something that you as the council do not like.
You have your alternative.
asking for the man, alternative measure to be presented, which would go to the devotee of the people at the same time.
As together, the voters approve one, and this group, the other, the one that they approve of the faculty departments in the city,
if they approve of, which could well happen, then the measure that received the most affirmed in that of us,
you kind of, the ordinance of the city, and the other one, those were the major things in the process,
but I think the work for you to understand right now that that will be glad to have done the question,
and of course as soon as we know what this is about, but you know what?
The question you keep saying that today, today is, I'm sorry.
The question, they are the reflection of the legal agencies and the folks associated with the agencies.
Do you have any thoughts on what to do with money?
The only thing that they gave me is they told me that there was something that I personally would want.
And that, that's scary because I really don't know what that means.
But I don't know what that means.
Well, that will create your views, and or something.
Then the right, just like in a way that it is, they're most involved in the environmental issues,
and that's why I know the man is that they brought the legal parking lot to us.
Then involved in a lot of environmental issues.
They don't work with that town.
The rest of our center, the senior center, is thinking about that.
So they can very often, but I understand that.
I believe that a basic idea for local environmental action.
That's why I know.
Any other questions you've been?
Any questions you've been?
Any questions you've been going into?
All right.
We want to 15 of you as a defendant.
This is the first thing we'll listen to.
You've seen it in staff and works.
17.
Mayor.
Perhaps a community.
An office.
18.
28.
Do we love the moment?
Do you want to have anything to go to the point?
No.
I can't.
Go move.
Second.
All right.
We'll send you.